=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 20=
(Lanruo Hall)
This human girl is quite pretty.
Hahaha.
Where are you going?
Let me go! Let me go!
Let's have some more fun.
Demon! Leave her alone!
Who are you?
You are asking for death.
This is Yu Linjun's domain now.
How dare a mere human act so arrogantly.
I will skin you alive
and hang you on the city gate.
Let all humans know
what happens when you cross us.
Heaven's Return Art.
(I've seen this technique before...)
Heaven and earth, lend me power.
All spirits, heed my call.
Lanxi, I'll go take a look.
Hey.
Are you messing with us?
Heaven and earth, lend me power.
All spirits, heed my call.
(The Wind God Chronicle
is coming from Ziyan...)
(But Ziyan...)
(why do you look at me like
I'm a stranger?)
(This technique is impressive.)
(This person)
(could be useful.)
Who dares ruin my fun?
I will kill you.
Inside Lanruo Hall,
humans and demons are equal.
Those who break the rules shall die.
Run! Run! Run!
Who are you?
(Could Yu Linjun be behind this?)
Do you truly not remember me?
(There is one way)
(to use the Divine Stone
to mend the sky)
(and still keep you alive.)
(My Demon Core
can serve as a vessel for the Stone.)
(This path is fraught with danger.)
(And once the Stone is removed
from her body,)
(she will lose everything about you.)
Staring at me with such longing,
are you trying to get my attention
and win my favor?
Ziyan,
don't tell me
you actually like this human.
What are you saying? I am a demon.
Why would I waste my thoughts on him?
He is nothing but a servant.
If you like him,
we can share him together.
Then I won't hold back.
A young Taoist,
I've never tasted one before.
I bet he's delicious.
Lanxi, didn't you use to hate
men coming near us?
What changed
after you came back?
Life is short.
Enjoy it while you can.
Once you find the cure and eat him,
we can live out our days together.
(Lanruo Hall)
Young Taoist,
that technique you used was interesting.
Teach me.
I will teach you.
Mind anchored in virtue.
Focus your spirit.
Banish demonic influence.
Let righteousness shine.
Hmm.
(Mind anchored in virtue.)
(Focus your spirit.)
(Banish demonic influence.)
(Let righteousness shine.)
(When you master this art,)
(then even if I'm gone,)
(you can protect yourself)
(and suffer no more.)
(I searched everywhere)
(and this young Taoist is my cure.)
Why did you teach me this?
You want to eat me.
But the bite mark hasn't appeared.
Eating me won't help.
Only I can make it appear.
Let's make a deal.
Join me.
We kill Yu Linjun.
So that's why you came to me.
After we mend the Sky Rift,
I'm yours.
What makes you think I'd agree?
You will.
(If he's really my cure,)
(let's see what he's got.)
(That mark...)
(Could it be...)
(Stone Curse?)
(My Lord, have you felt
anything strange lately?)
The Stone's memories
of the Mortal Realm are gone.
Even the Wind God technique
can't stop me now.
But why
when I tried to consume her,
why could Chi Xiao stop me?
(Chi Xiao is your incarnation.)
(He loves the Stone.)
(That's why he protected her
without thinking.)
So that's why I can't devour her.
(That is one reason.)
(You and the Demon Queen
were once one Stone.)
(Split in two by accident.)
(But two halves of the same Stone
repel each other.)
No matter what,
I'll devour
the whole Divine Stone
and rule both realms.
(Chi Xiao's love for the Stone
is bound to you.)
(If you force it,)
(the Stone will fight back,)
(and Chi Xiao's love)
(will tear you apart.)
Then tell me,
what should I do?
(Make the other half of the Stone
fall in love.)
(Make Shangguan Ziyan love you.)
(Then,)
(your Demon Flower
and her Love Flower will merge.)
(Only then can you devour her.)
Love? Please.
I have no use for it.
Is there another way?
(Find someone she deeply loves.)
(That can also
make her Love Flower bloom.)
(Besides Shangguan Lanxi,)
(I know of one other.)
(She raised the Demon Queen
since childhood.)
(Their bond is sincere and deep.)
It is your honor
to catch our Lord's eye.
Stay in line.
Senior.
Yuanchu.
Look at me.
Senior.
What are you going to do?
Ziyan.
There's someone in there I need to save.
You don't have a shred of power left.
And you want to charge in and die?
Senior.
I'm starving today.
So I'll keep this
rather unimpressive thing.
I...
Our Lord is waiting.
I won't say it twice.
The Demon Queen is precious to our Lord.
We wouldn't dare disobey.
Ha.
The rest of you, come with me.
Yuanchu.
Hurry!
You scared me to death!
I thought you were dead.
Oh, thank goodness.
I am so glad you are alright.
I am fine.
Are you okay?
Mm.
Ziyan, thank goodness.
You are safe too.
Master.
I didn't fail you.
Yuanchu,
I recall Master said before his death.
There is a demon poison.
that, when combined
with Heavenly Justice,
Tearless Tear, and Underworld Soul,
can kill any demon in this world.
The stronger the demon,
the deadlier the poison.
This young man has a kind heart.
Though we have never met before,
you've given me such useful information.
We've never met?
Ziyan,
have you forgotten your lovable,
mighty senior?
We used to...
Ziyan has lost her memories.
She doesn't remember
everything about the Mortal Realm,
including us.
Don't worry.
Whether you remember me or not,
you will always be my dear friend
and sister-in-law.
I will find a way
to bring your memories back.
Speaking of the day we met,
it was a bright sunny afternoon.
We were together...
Enough!
I only trust my own memories.
Ah?
(Ziyan,)
(how can I make you remember me?)
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪